domainsite.com 2006-03-24

# DomainSite.com

We respect your privacy. We do not sell or rent your personal information to third parties for marketing purposes without your explicit consent. According to the law, domain name registration information has to be made available through Whois…, a publicly accessible database that lists the domain name registration information of each registrant. Since domain name registration information is available to the public through Whois…, anyone can access it on the Domainsite.com website or other web resources that offer Whois…. Therefore, the domain name registration information you provide us is, and must be, made available to the public. At times our customers may be included within searches of the Whois… database; however, any "spam" received through the use of Whois… does not originate from Domainsite.com. 

The privacy policy of this statement applies to our services offered under the domain name Domainsite.com and to our subsidiaries or joint venture websites. We promise that we will not use your personal information in any way that is incompatible with this privacy policy. By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. This privacy policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the Domainsite.com Registration Agreement. Please do not use or access the Domainsite.com website if you do not agree to this privacy policy. 

Our website uses WebTrends Live to analyze traffic. Unlike some tracking services, WebTrends Live does not create individual profiles for visitors. WebTrends Live only collects aggregate data. Please read the following excerpt from WebTrends Live's Privacy Principles to learn more about the ways your personal information will be used and protected. To learn even more about WebTrends Live's privacy policy, please click here.  

WebTrends Live--Privacy Principles*  
Because your trust and confidence is important to us, WebTrends Live conducts its business under the following privacy principles: 

Principle 1 \- No Collection of Personal Information  
WebTrends Live does not collect any personal information such as names, ages, phone numbers, addresses or e-mail addresses from visitors to Domainsite.com's website. 

Principle 2 \- No Combination of Browsing and Web Traffic Information with Personal Information  
Since WebTrends Live does not collect any personal information from website visitors, we do not combine traffic analysis information with personal information such as name, age, phone number or mailing address. 

Principle 3 \- No Aggregation of Individual Visitor Traffic Patterns across Multiple Sites  
WebTrends Live does not collect individual profile information for visitors across multiple sites and does not aggregate information from any other sources about browsing patterns of individual visitors across multiple sites. 

Principle 4 \- Collection of Non-Personally Identifiable Information   
WebTrends Live collects anonymous visitor information like IP addresses, browser types (such as Internet Explorer or Netscape), referring pages, pages visited and time spent on the web site. WebTrends Live collects this non-personally identifiable information for the following purposes: (1) to provide anonymous statistical analysis of web page traffic patterns to Domainsite.com for its website; (2) to administer our website and servers, (3) to allow for auditing of our services by third parties, and (4) to improve our services. 

Principle 5 \- Anonymous Use of Cookies  
It is WebTrends Live's policy to use cookies only for more accurate anonymous traffic analysis such as tracking the time/date of the visit, the page viewed, the referrer, transaction information for eCommerce pages. The cookie information does not include personal data such as name, age, phone number, e-mail address or mailing address. In addition, WebTrends Live does not link cookies to personal data such as name, age, phone number, e-mail address or mailing address. As we do not build a database of individual visitors, the data that we do collect is never stored in any individual user profile; the data collected serves only to update aggregate counts allowing Domainsite.com to monitor traffic on its site. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you would prefer, you can set your browser to reject cookies.   
Through WebTrends Live, Domainsite.com uses customized JavaScript tracking code provided by WebTrends to track anonymous information about its website visitors' activity. This code contacts NetIQ's servers, receives a response, and loads an image to the page. This 1x1 image is called a clear gif or web bug. This JavaScript tracking code does not collect personal information such as name, age, phone number, mailing address or credit card numbers from visitors to Domainsite.com's website. Visitors may elect to opt out of receiving tracking cookies for all sites using WebTrends Live services. 

Principle 6 \- No Individual Profiling  
WebTrends Live does not create individual profiles of visitors. Unlike other tracking services we do not have a database of individual profiles of each visitor. WebTrends Live collects data in aggregate form and data is not recorded or stored about individual visitors. 

Principle 7 \- Third Party Access  
Domainsite.com controls access to WebTrends Live traffic analysis reports. WebTrends Live does not provide access to anyone other than the visitors identified by Domainsite.com. WebTrends Live anonymous traffic data for Domainsite.com may be provided to an auditing service upon request from Domainsite.com.   

Principle 8 \- Opting Out of Tracking Cookies  
You may elect to opt out of receiving tracking cookies for all sites using WebTrends Live services. To do so, you will need to accept a cookie indicating your choice. Please visit our opt-out page for more information.   

For More Information  
For more information about WebTrends Live privacy policy, please click here.  
*Excerpted From WebTrends Live: http://www.webtrendslive.com/wtl_system/privacy_policy.htm  

Notice:  
Domainsite.com may amend this privacy policy at any time by posting the amendment terms to the Domainsite.com website. All amendments shall automatically be effective 30 days after they are initially posted to the Domainsite.com website.
